export const chapter = "Chapter - 27: Unpacking Gender";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is the primary basis for people's understanding of gender roles in ordinary life?",
        optionA: "Biological distinctions",
        optionB: "Cultural and traditional values",
        optionC: "Economic status",
        correctAnswer: "B. Cultural and traditional values",
      },
      {
        question:
          "According to the text, what does the term 'stereotype' refer to?",
        optionA: "Fixed ideas that are normally true",
        optionB: "Prejudices and power relations between men and women",
        optionC: "Unusual behaviors in society",
        correctAnswer:
          "B. Prejudices and power relations between men and women",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the ancient times of the country discussed in the text, what was the status of women compared to men?",
        optionA: "Women had a superior status",
        optionB: "Women and men enjoyed equal status",
        optionC: "Women had a subordinate status",
        correctAnswer: "B. Women and men enjoyed equal status",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which agency is mentioned as the starting point for gender inequality in the text?",
        optionA: "Educational Institutions",
        optionB: "Family",
        optionC: "Place of Work",
        correctAnswer: "B. Family",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What crime is committed when a girl-child is killed soon after her birth?",
        optionA: "Female Foeticide",
        optionB: "Child Marriage",
        optionC: "Female Infanticide",
        correctAnswer: "C. Female Infanticide",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What has the government done to address crimes against women in the text?",
        optionA: "Launched awareness campaigns",
        optionB: "Passed laws making such crimes punishable",
        optionC: "Encouraged stereotypes",
        correctAnswer: "B. Passed laws making such crimes punishable",
      },
      {
        question:
          "According to the text, what is the main focus of the Sakhi Movement?",
        optionA: "Promoting stereotypes",
        optionB: "Improving women's status in society",
        optionC: "Encouraging female infanticide",
        correctAnswer: "B. Improving women's status in society",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is mentioned as a powerful tool in the hands of girls to make them aware of their rights and responsibilities?",
        optionA: "Economic status",
        optionB: "Laws",
        optionC: "Education",
        correctAnswer: "C. Education",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is one of the reservations provided by the government to improve the condition of women, as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Reservation in sports",
        optionB:
          "Reservation in education, employment, and local self-government",
        optionC: "Reservation in cultural events",
        correctAnswer:
          "B. Reservation in education, employment, and local self-government",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How does the text suggest improving the status of women in the family and society?",
        optionA: "Through economic empowerment",
        optionB: "Through awareness and acceptance as equal partners",
        optionC: "Through stricter laws",
        correctAnswer: "B. Through awareness and acceptance as equal partners",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "In ordinary life, people's understanding about gender is often based on the ________ and ________ of their family and society.",
        options: [
          "Economic status, traditions",
          "Roles, values",
          "Culture, education",
        ],
        answer: "Roles, values",
      },
      {
        question:
          "'Gender' refers to the inequalities and power relations between men and women in ________.",
        options: ["Workplaces", "Families", "Society"],
        answer: "Society",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The distinction between boys and girls in society is based on ________.",
        options: [
          "Biological factors",
          "Individual preferences",
          "Family and societal values",
        ],
        answer: "Family and societal values",
      },
      {
        question: "Stereotypes are fixed ideas that may not be _________.",
        options: ["Normal", "Accurate", "Traditional"],
        answer: "Accurate",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Gender inequality became more prevalent in the society during the medieval period due to _________.",
        options: ["Cultural values", "Invasions", "Educational reforms"],
        answer: "Invasions",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The primary responsibility of the President of India is representing the ________ of the state.",
        options: ["Judiciary", "Legislature", "Head"],
        answer: "Head",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The government has enacted several laws to protect girls' and women's dignity, including laws against crimes such as foeticide, infanticide, and _________.",
        options: ["Child Marriage", "Dowry demand", "Triple Talaq"],
        answer: "Triple Talaq",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Sakhi Movement focuses on improving women's status in ________.",
        options: ["Families", "Society", "Workplaces"],
        answer: "Society",
      },
      {
        question:
          "One step to improve women's status is providing ________ for them in education, employment, and local self-government.",
        options: ["Reservations", "Stereotypes", "Movements"],
        answer: "Reservations",
      },
      {
        question:
          "According to the text, girls and women can become equal partners when they are accepted as equals in the ________ and ________.",
        options: [
          "Workplace, community",
          "Family, society",
          "Educational system, government",
        ],
        answer: "Family, society",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The Preamble to the Constitution of India incorporates the vision and aspirations of the Indian people.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "India is a sovereign nation, which means it can make laws without interference from other countries.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Secularism in India means that the state gives equal importance to all religions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In a democratic government, elected representatives are the supreme power.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The President of India is the head of both the nation and the government.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "The Indian Constitution has a total of 500 Articles.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Fundamental Duties were included in the Indian Constitution in 1976.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Directive Principles of State Policy can be enforced by the Judiciary.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "India is a federal nation, which means powers are divided among the central government, state government, and local self-government.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Constitution of India came into force on August 15, 1947.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
